It's nice to meet you!
The beastmen from Howling Village moved here.
If you need anything, just ask Lamulias.
She's the housing manager.
It's nice to meet you.
Yes!
Uh, you don't need to be that formal...
Apparently, they all thought
that they were going to be treated
horribly when they moved here.
Naturally, we have no such intentions.
There doesn't seem to be any apparent
problem with the new residents, however...
However?
They faint quite often.
Well, they'll just have to get
used to things here.
Farming Life in Another World
Masshiro hikari no naka me o samashite
hajimatteiku sutoorii
Fumidasu atarashii sekai donna hana o sakaseyou?
Kumori sora datte mizutamari de yogoretatte
Bokura wa susumu
Souzou mo shinai mirai ga matteiru kitto
Deatte deatte tsunagatteku
Waraeba mawari mo egao ni naru
Chiisana tane maite sodateyou
Yagate ookina hana ni naru
Koukai ya shippai wa kate ni shite
Karafuru na shiawase de afureru youni
Bokura te o toriatte wakeatte
Sekaijuu ni hirogatteike Flower Ring
Wait up!
Come on!
Jeez, you need to be
more careful when you play.
You can use magic too, Sena?
Yes, I can.
Don't tell me... am I the only one here
who can't use magic?
Well, all of the angels can use magic...
Yes.
All of the high elves can use magic.
It's common for us to be able to use
fire and water magic.
We're good with water.
Even the bees can do it.
Don't worry!
You're not the only one
who can't use magic!
Let's practice together.
Yeah, you're right.
I have a feeling these kids
will surpass me, too.
Oh well. There's no point
in wishing for the impossible.
I'll just focus on what I can do for now.
What was that? An earthquake?
Mayor!
A grappler bear and a bloody viper are
fighting in the northern area of the forest!
Bear and viper?
A bear and a snake?
Them fighting with each other is enough
to make the ground shake this much?
What shall we do?
Hm... a bear and a snake?
If this keeps up, it might affect the village.
But it would be dangerous to get
involved without a plan.
That's true.
So about those animals...
do you think we can eat them?
So anyways, I've heard that hunters
sometimes eat bear meat.
I've always wondered how they taste.
Okay...
There they are!
Wow, they're big.
Let's go back for help!
No. Just take me down really fast.
Understood.
It's been a while since I got a big one.
One... Two...
What's wrong?
Could you take down a monster
like that with one attack?
No way.
Yeah... the mayor is something else.
Looking at him up close, he really is huge.
As far as cooking them goes,
what do you plan to make?
I've got some ideas.
I'll add in some of these herbs and spices.
Now we add wine and simmer.
Our precious wine?!
It's fine. That kind of cooking is normal.
Wine Braised Grappler Bear
And there we have it,
wine braised grappler bear.
It's incredibly gamey.
Our precious wine...
I'm telling you this is normal.
Chicken-fried Bloody Viper
And this is the blood viper.
I tried frying it.
This tastes just like fried chicken!
It's great!
It tastes different than I expected.
It tastes surprisingly like chicken breast.
Which means my plate is missing
something that goes right here.
Flora's Lab
So then, what brings you here today?
I was wondering if you had anything
that could act as an anti-bacterial agent.
Anti-bacterial?
Yeah. I need it for a new recipe
I want to try.
Do you have any medicines that can
kill harmful microorganisms?
Microorganisms!
Those are the things you spoke of before!
Yeah, that's them.
I want something that will prevent
stomach aches or illness.
I see.
Leave it to me!
Ah, how about this one?
One dose is enough to blast anything
to the other side of the mountains.
Do you have anything that's more peaceful?
Then how about this one?
This one is safe to use in foods.
Yeah, this will work.
Thanks.
Of course.
By the way, how's the
miso production coming along?
The truth is, it's not going very well.
I did everything exactly like you told me to,
but no matter how long I waited it never
seemed like it was starting to ferment.
I've had to rebuild my hut three times.
That's not supposed to happen.
Well, let's give it another try.
Can we?!
I'll try to keep the explosives to a minimum!
Please don't use any.
There we go. That looks good.
First, we beat the eggs.
Then we add salt and vinegar.
By the way, this vinegar
is made from apples.
That's also fermented, right?
Then we mix it as we slowly add in the oil.
And now we have mayonnaise.
Now it's exactly like having fried chicken!
Wow! I can eat this stuff by itself!
Stop that right now.
It's terrible for your health.
Now then, on to making miso.
First, we start by simmering
the soybeans we soaked in water.
Then we grind them.
Moldy, moldy, moldy, mold!
Moldy, moldy, moldy...
I used the almighty farming tool
to help make the koji mold.
Moldy, moldy, moldy...
I used the almighty farming tool
to help make the koji mold.
You don't need to write that down.
We mixed the koji with salt
and formed balls.
Now we pack it into barrels.
I see.
Mine didn't work because
I didn't say moldy, moldy, mold.
No, that's... well, maybe.
Now we just let it age in the cellar.
It'll take a few months,
so let's wait patiently.
That long?
Yeah.
But all that time will make
the flavors even more intense.
This requires perseverance,
just like research.
Yup.
Ah, there you are.
You've got visitors.
Visitors?
The visitors were a group of dwarves
led by a man named Donovan.
We're elder dwarves.
What's the difference?
We've heard that you have
high quality alcohol in this village,
and we'd like you to share some with us.
You mean our wine?
I'd be happy to share with you...
Mayor. We can't give it away for free.
Huh?
She's right. Our wine is very valuable.
Yeah, but they're our guests...
I'm sorry, but we don't have money.
However, we do have technology.
Technology?
That's right.
We've spent our lives
studying alcohol production,
and we've traveled a long way to get here.
You have some very fine
crops in this village.
We can help you turn them
into fine alcohol.
What do you think?
Don't you want to drink some?
Donovan and his men got to work
on the alcohol right away.
Distillation... I remember doing this
in science class.
Here you go. This is corn whiskey.
It's crystal clear.
It'll get its color when we
age it in barrels.
I see.
This is strong!
I guess the mayor is a lightweight.
Donovan and his men ended up staying
in the village and working as our brewers.
Now that we've got new alcohol,
it's time to have a welcome party for
the beastmen and the dwarves!
Drink up, everyone!
You can really taste the fragrance
when you drink this alcohol.
I really like this mayonnaise.
This goes perfect with the booze.
Let's drink all night!
He snuck in again...
I don't mind that he comes here,
but he always drinks too much.
Alright! It's time to show you all
my special technique!
Thanks for everything, mayor.
It was kind of you to take us all in.
Don't mention it.
We're all happy you're here.
Yeah, there are a lot of people
in this village who like to drink.
Wait a minute, I finally got some
adult men to join the village.
By the way, Donovan.
I'm not asking for any particular reason, but...
are there any girls here who catch your eye?
You know, the kind that make you
think "Wow, she's pretty!"?
Well they're all very good looking,
but you know, I think they're all
a little too young for me...
If they can't at least grow a beard,
then they're not for me.
A-a beard?
Man, why are you making me
say it out loud...
The cultural barrier is high.
Farming Life...
in Anoooother...
World.
Don't tell me there's another wyvern.
Wait, a dragon?!
It's headed straight for us,
and it doesn't look friendly.
I'm going to finish this one off before it
causes any damage to the village.
What?
Isn't that... Dryme?!
Is this infighting?
But they're just staring each other down now.
There's another one?!
That one's dangerous!
I missed...
But the next one won't!
Please wait!
That isn't an enemy!
I'm terribly sorry for the confusion.
These two are my master's wife
and his daughter.
I'm Lastismoon.
My name is Graffaloon.
N-nice to meet you. I'm Hiraku Machio.
Why are your wife and daughter here?
Well, you see...
Apparently, Dryme's constant sneaking out
so that he could come to our village
has roused some suspicions at home.
What were we supposed to think
when he was sneaking out every night?
If it turned out that he really was
sneaking out to do something he shouldn't...
What a ridiculous accusation.
But you were sneaking off with
all kinds of stuff from the treasury!
And you'd always be out
till the next morning.
Ah, I get it now.
It's the gifts he always brings us.
Dryme's House
And I was worried about him
going home drunk, so I built him a house.
Maybe that wasn't such a good idea.
That was all for the sake of
our diplomatic relations!
It was all very high-level politics,
you see, and uh...
He's hiding something.
It was all very high-level politics,
you see, and uh...
Indeed.
At this point...
my suspicions...
are all being confirmed.
She's scary.
Wait a minute, you two!
Just think about it!
Do you think this man...
even has the courage...
to have an affair like that?!
That's a good point.
Ah, thank goodness.
Are you all happy with that?
Um, excuse me.
Even though I didn't know who you were,
I'm sorry about how I acted earlier.
No, don't worry about it.
This was all our fault.
Come on you two, apologize!
I'm sorry I was about to
burn the village down
because I thought my dad
was having an affair.
And I'm sorry that I was about to
obliterate the insolent man
who pointed a spear at my daughter.
They're scary!
Well, I guess everything's settled now.
But dear, you still shouldn't be
sneaking out to get drunk like that.
What are you talking about?!
That's right.
You get out of hand when you drink!
Well, I'm just glad to see that
they're getting along.
Okay, see you later.
Yeah.
Do you understand what I was doing now?
Yes.
Our relationship with this village
is of the utmost importance.
Despite their lack of numbers,
they still have the power necessary
to challenge us.
I never thought we'd meet anyone
that had the strength to overwhelm us.
You're right...
You couldn't even defend against that attack.
You had to avoid it.
Even that was only thanks to the spider.
Spider?
Yes. An old friend of mine.
Had I not been pulled out of the way;
I may not be standing here now.
Lasty.
Y-yes?
I have a very important job for you.
I want you to live here for a while.
Mother?
Wh-where's this coming from?
Please keep your mouth shut, darling.
Okay.
We can't ignore that kind of power.
I don't expect you to be able to suppress it,
I just expect you to do your duty
and make sure that such power
is never turned against us dragons.
Is that understood?
Yes. I'll do my best.
Are you sure about this?
Yes. I believe that choosing this path
will lead to the best outcome for Lasty.
I can feel it.
Sure, I don't mind.
I look forward to working together!
If you wouldn't mind,
please call me Lasty!
Yeah, sounds good.
So, what should I do here?
Let's see...
And so, Lasty immediately
went to work in the village.
How about you start helping
with the harvesting?
And so, Lasty immediately
went to work in the village.
I'm ready to start now!
A-are you a dragon?
However...
Huh?
...dragons are pretty extraordinary
in all regards.
Gently...
It looks like it'll take a while
for her to get used to her work.
Wait up!
What should we do with her?
Well, you don't need to make her do
something she isn't a fit for.
But Dryme told me to give her work
to do around here.
What is it?
They've been like this ever since
all the dragons showed up here.
The cows and chickens
have all be scared, too.
We haven't been able to get
any milk or eggs.
Ah...
That
Dryme acts like that,
so I wasn't really thinking about it,
but everyone is normally
afraid of dragons, aren't they?
It's not just power they have, either.
Their knowledge and wisdom are also great.
In that case...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Don't worry about i...
I'm Lastismoon, and I'm currently
in charge of handling
diplomatic relations here at the village.
D-don't tell you me you're that dragon girl...
I am! Please call me Lasty.
What is it that you've come to
request from us today?
F-first off, we'd like some more of those
bright colored fruit we got last time...
You mean the oranges, right?
I'm sorry to say that our stock of them
is running quite low at the moment...
Could I interest you in
some strawberries instead?
They're perfectly ripe now.
I-in that case, I'll take ten boxes of those.
Thank you so much!
Could I interest you in some apples
and pears to go with them?
We have persimmons and
watermelons as well.
O-okay, I'll take those as well.
Here's your order.
Thank you very much.
Would you like to count them
to confirm the order?
That won't be necessary!
Very well then.
We look forward to seeing you again.
It looks like she's got the hang of this.
What?!
They have dragons now? Is this a joke?!
That village's military might
grows by the day.
We need to monitor them.
Should we send a spy there now?
If they find out, they'll consider it
an act of aggression!
We have no other choice.
I have a plan.
Pardon me.
You called for me, Father?
Yes.
Flowrem, have a seat there.
I see.
So, I'm to investigate that village, correct?
Yes. In particular, their military might.
However, you mustn't do anything rash.
Your safety must always be
your number one concern.
Understood.
But I am your daughter, after all.
I'm confident in my magical abilities.
Don't worry about me.
At a glance, this seems like
just an ordinary village, but...
how did they develop a village like this
in the middle of a forest filled with
such terrifying monsters?
Welcome to The Great Tree Village.
I'm Lastismoon,
the head of diplomatic relations.
I-it's nice to meet you.
You're going to stay here
in this village for a while, right?
I heard from Beezel.
Call me Lasty.
Isn't Lastismoon...
that infamous dragon
that everyone is afraid of?
I can't believe I've already met
someone this powerful.
What's wrong?
I'm going to show you around the village.
O-okay!
And this here is our vineyard.
We can make delicious wine
from these grapes here!
My father said that the wine here
is the most delicious in all the lands!
This seems like just an ordinary vineyard.
My father said that the wine here
is the most delicious in all the lands!
This seems like just an ordinary vineyard.
Roar!
Why is a legendary dragon in a place like
this bragging to me about crops they're growing?
Roar! Roar!
Why is a legendary dragon in a place like
this bragging to me about crops they're growing?
Roar!
Why is a legendary dragon in a place like
this bragging to me about crops they're growing?
And get this, so then my dad told me that...
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I've spotted a messenger
from Howling Village.
Oh, okay!
Sorry, I need to go take care of something.
Don't worry about it.
I'll just have a look around on my own.
Okay, see you later.
This works out perfectly.
I can take the opportunity to analyze
their military strength.
Those are lizardmen.
Beastmen and ogres.
And even dwarves?
They'll all be tough to deal with,
but with the full force of our military
we might be able to handle them.
This might be their headquarters.
The vampire princess.
It won't have enough firepower like this.
I heard she was on the run from nobles,
so she was laying low.
Okay, then let's add twice as much.
I heard she was on the run from nobles,
so she was laying low.
Okay, then let's add twice as much.
What's she doing here?
Our aerial defenses in this area
have been getting neglected lately.
The angel of annihilation, Tia.
Our aerial defenses in this area
have been getting neglected lately.
Why is she in the same village as Lulucy?
Let's make sure we're trying our hardest here.
The safety of the village rests in our hands.
And I'm pretty sure I heard that those three
are called the trio of killer angels.
Yes.
And I'm pretty sure I heard that those three
are called the trio of killer angels.
They even have high elves here?
You look sleepy.
I've heard that those are
the terrifying maneaters
Good morning.
I've heard that those are
the terrifying maneaters
Good morning.
that prey upon helpless young men
and kidnap them.
Good morning.
that prey upon helpless young men
and kidnap them.
If there are five of them here,
then this is already too much
for our military to handle...
Impossible!
They have inferno wolves
and demon spiders!
And they've formed one single pack!
Up until now, I've been proud to call myself
one of the most talented magic users
in all of the demon kingdom, but...
I feel like all my confidence has left me.
To command all of these powerful troops,
it would make sense to assume that Lastismoon
was in charge of such an organization.
But there's someone above her
called the mayor who rules over all of them.
What kind of terrifying opponent
am I dealing with?
Huh?
It's just a human?
Why is a human here of all places?
What are you doing here?
Are you lost or something?
Don't worry about me!
I'm not so weak that I need an ordinary human
to be worrying about me.
What? That person I saw just now?!
Yup. That's the mayor.
But isn't he just an ordinary human?
He's a human strong enough
to defeat my mom.
That can't be!
Did you say hello?
Forget saying hello,
I was outright rude to him...
There we go.
I found out that girl was Beezel's daughter.
Apparently, she's going to
live here for a while.
I'll give you a hand.
She seems to be getting along well with Lasty.
That's great and all, but...
Good morning, mayor!
G-good morning.
I hope you have a lovely day!
...for some reason,
she acted like this for a while.
Kisetsu no kaze fuwari yubisaki de sotto kanjiru
Sora ni ukabu kumo ni daisuki sagasou
Tokei no hari wa ima wa wasure
Shinkokyuu hitotsu shitemiyouyo
Nanairo no keshiki kokoro hibiku
Donna negai koto demo kanau ki ga suru
Kimi ga soba ni iru nara
Yume mitaina hibi o kuretan dayo
Atatakakute yasashii basho de
Itsumademo egao o miseteite
Next Time
Episode 9
The Merchant and the Dragon
Next Time